<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<translations>
<en-GB>

<name>League Preferences Administration</name>
<menu-lge>League Preferences</menu-lge>
<help>Using the league prefences league and global administrators can change some of the settings for a league without modifying the PHP files.</help>

<lname>League</lname>

<prime_title>Primary Tournament</prime_title>
<prime_help>The primary tournament is used for the front page league table</prime_help>

<second_title>Primary Division</second_title>
<second_help>The primary division is used for front page player performance stats</second_help>

<league_name_title>League Name</league_name_title>
<league_name_help>Name of your league</league_name_help>

<forum_url_title>Forum URL</forum_url_title>
<forum_url_help>The link to use in the Forum button on the main menu. Leave this blank for no forum.</forum_url_help>

<welcome_title>Welcome</welcome_title>
<welcome_help>Message to appear at the top of the home page. This can be HTML.</welcome_help>

<rules_title>League Rules</rules_title>
<rules_help>The rules to display under the Rules menu. This can be HTML.</rules_help>


<submit_text>OK</submit_text>
<submit_title>Update this league`s preferences</submit_title>

<failedSave>Unable to save preferences</failedSave>
<failedValidate>Oh Noes! The league administration module has failed the ptid!=stid check.  Please alert your administrator!</failedValidate>
<failedSave>Sorry, you don't have permission to update this league</failedSave>

<saved>Updated</saved>

<css_title>League CSS&lt;br/&gt; &lt;i&gt;(careful if you don't know CSS)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You may need to clear cache after editing.</css_title>
<css_help>You can theme your League, but you need to know CSS!</css_help>

<core_theme_title>Core Theme</core_theme_title>
<core_theme_help>These are pre-built themes you can use, or build from using the League CSS below.</core_theme_help>

<tv_title>Initial Treasury</tv_title>
<tv_help>Usually set this to 1000000, but you can pick other values.</tv_help>

<language_title>Language</language_title>
<language_help>Your leagues default language.</language_help>


</en-GB>

<fr-FR>

<name>Administration de Ligue</name>
<menu-lge>Préférences de Ligue</menu-lge>
<help>Les préférences de Ligue permettent aux Administrateurs généraux et de la ligue de modifier certains paramètres sans toucher aux fichiers PHP.</help>

<lname>Ligue</lname>

<prime_title>Tournoi principal</prime_title>
<prime_help>Le tournoi principal affiché sur la page d'accueil</prime_help>

<second_title>Division principale</second_title>
<second_help>La division principale est utilisée en page d'accueil des statistiques et performances de joueur</second_help>

<league_name_title>Nom de la Ligue</league_name_title>
<league_name_help>Nom de votre Ligue</league_name_help>

<forum_url_title>URL du Forum</forum_url_title>
<forum_url_help>Lien à utiliser pour le bouton Forum dans le menu principal. Laissez vide s'il n'y a pas de forum.</forum_url_help>

<welcome_title>Bienvenue</welcome_title>
<welcome_help>Message apparaissant en haut de la page d'accueil. Peut contenir de l'HTML.</welcome_help>

<rules_title>Règles de Ligue</rules_title>
<rules_help>Les règles à afficher sous le menu Règles. Peut contenir de l'HTML.</rules_help>


<submit_text>OK</submit_text>
<submit_title>Mettre à jour les préférences de Ligue</submit_title>

<failedSave>Impossible d'enregistrer les préférences</failedSave>
<failedValidate>Oh Non ! Le module d'administration de ligue a échoue dans le test du ptid!=stid. Prenez contact avec votre administrateur !</failedValidate>
<failedSave>Désolé, vous n'avez pas les permissions pour mettre à jour la ligue.</failedSave>

<saved>Mis à jour</saved>

<css_title>CSS de Ligue&lt;br/&gt; &lt;i&gt;(prenez garde si vous ne connaissez pas le CSS)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Il faudra sans doute vider votre cache après la mise à jour.</css_title>
<css_help>Vous pouvez modifier le thème CSS de votre ligue, si vous vous y connaissez !</css_help>

<core_theme_title>Thème principal</core_theme_title>
<core_theme_help>Ce sont des thèmes existants que vous pouvez utiliser tel quel ou comme base en modifiant ensuite le CSS.</core_theme_help>

<tv_title>Trésorerie de départ</tv_title>
<tv_help>Généralement placée à 1.000.000, mais libre à vous de modifier cette valeur.</tv_help>

<language_title>Langue</language_title>
<language_help>La langue par défaut de votre Ligue.</language_help>


</fr-FR>
</translations>